{
  "collection": {
    "name": "French - Czech - Čísla",
    "description": "French - Czech - Čísla",
    "hidden": "false"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "cent",
      "back": "sto",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "cinq",
      "back": "pět",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "cinquante",
      "back": "padesát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "dix",
      "back": "deset",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "dix-huit",
      "back": "osmnáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "dix-neuf",
      "back": "devatenáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "huit",
      "back": "osm",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "mille",
      "back": "tisíc",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "mille",
      "back": "tisíc",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "million",
      "back": "milion, milión",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "neuf",
      "back": "devět",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "onze",
      "back": "jedenáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "paire",
      "back": "pár",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quarante",
      "back": "čtyřicet",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quatorze",
      "back": "čtrnáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quatre",
      "back": "čtyři",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quatre-vingt-dix",
      "back": "devadesát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quatre-vingts",
      "back": "osmdesát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "quinze",
      "back": "patnáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "rien",
      "back": "nic, nula",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "seize",
      "back": "šestnáct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "sept",
      "back": "sedm",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "six",
      "back": "šest",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "soixante",
      "back": "šedesát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "soixante-dix",
      "back": "sedmdesát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "treize",
      "back": "třináct",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "trente",
      "back": "třicet",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "trois",
      "back": "tři",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "troisième",
      "back": "třetí",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "un",
      "back": "jeden",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "vingt",
      "back": "dvacet",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Čísla",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    }
  ],
  "settings": {
    "id": 1,
    "playVoiceText": "true",
    "languageOfVoice": "fr",
    "typeOfVoice": "f2",
    "volumeOfVoice": 100,
    "displayAnswer": "false",
    "displayAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "limitTAnswer": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTime": 60,
    "showAnswerTime": "false",
    "limitTAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTimeByRepeating": 60,
    "showAnswerTimeByRepeating": "false",
    "filteringCards": "true"
  }
}
